

## Nguyễn MINH CHÍ

### Front End Developer

**Date of birth:** Feb 1, 1997

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 0349932192

**Email:** nmchiht@gmail.com

Address: Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh, Việt Nam

Website: https://bnportfolio.vercel.app/

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Take advantage of your existing skills and experience, learn new skills and technologies to become an expert in the near future, bringing a lot of value to your partner as well as your own development. From there, I will contribute to the development of the Company.

#### **EDUCATION**

DEC 2015 - NOV 2021

Thai Nguyen University of Information and Communication

Technology

Major: Information Technology

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Feb 2023 - Present

#### **FINANTAGED**

Front-end Developer

Web application development:

- Build and maintain web applications using ReactJs, NextJs,

Wordpress

- Optimize site performance and interactions to ensure the best user experience.
- Use libraries and tools like Axios, Redux Toolkit, Middleware.
- Manage application state, handle logic, and communicate with APIs.
- Fix bugs

User interface (UI) design:

- Based on the design from the design team, implemented a beautiful and user-friendly user interface that is responsive across different devices.
- Use CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap and Tailwind Css.
- Optimize user experience on mobile devices.

Source code management:

- Use Git to manage source code and work in different branches.

May 2022 - Present

#### **PERSONAL PROJECT**

Personal website:

- Build personal website using Next.js and Tailwind CSS.
- Use CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap and Tailwind Css for interface.
- Link demo: https://bnportfolio.vercel.app/

May 2022 - Present

### **FREELANCER**

Front-end Developer
Website GasCongNghiep
Website GreenHouse

- Build and maintain web applications using Wordpress
   Based on the design from the design team, responsive across different devices.
   Deploy system in Linux

  Jul 2021 Jan 2022

  VANO JSC
  Front-end Developer
  - Web application development:
     Build and maintain web applications using ReactJs, NextJs,
    Wordpress, Java Spring Boot
     Monitor, manage, control deployed websites, landing pages.
     Monitor the process of product implementation and operation to
  - improve and upgrade new features.
  - Fix bugs

Source code management:

- Deploy system in Linux
- Use Git to manage source code

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

2020	Bachelor of Information Technology from FPT APTECH

## **SKILLS**

Technologies	Reactjs, Nextjs, Nuxtjs, Tailwind CSS, Laravel, Wordpress, Bootstrap, PHP, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Java Spring Boot
Database	MySQL, MongoDB
Tools	Github, Bitbucket, MobaXterm, Gitlab
Language	English: Basic writing and reading
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint

## **PROJECTS**

## Beauty'I

(Oct 2023 - Current)

Customer	Finantaged
Description	Develop a website to introduce spa processes to customers in the beauty industry.
Team size	2
My position	Include coding HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create attractive and interactive user interfaces.
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Optimize user interface on different devices (responsive design).</li> <li>Integrate unique plugins and features like search bar, checkout</li> <li>Create about pages, and contact pages</li> <li>Ensure source code complies with SEO standards and optimizes page loading speed.</li> <li>Optimize website performance with rocket plugin</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Use WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Bootstrap Integrates plugins like Yoast SEO, WP Super Cache, elementor, rocket

#### Auvin

( Aug 2023 - Current)

Customer Finantaged	
---------------------	--

Description	Develop a website to alcohol, Building an e-commerce website for Auvin
Team size	2
My position	Include coding HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create attractive and interactive user interfaces.
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Optimize user interface on different devices (responsive design).</li> <li>Integrate unique plugins and features like search bar, shopping cart, checkout, and product reviews.</li> <li>Create product pages, categories, about pages, and contact pages.</li> <li>Ensure source code complies with SEO standards and optimizes page loading speed.</li> <li>Optimize website performance with rocket plugin</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Use WordPress, WooCommerce, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Bootstrap Integrates plugins like Yoast SEO, WP Super Cache, , elementor, rocket

# **Finantaged** (Apr 2023 - Current)

Customer	Finantaged
Description	Develop management, trade, and learning applications in the financial field.  The project is a web application that helps users learn about stock trading and trading strategies.
Team size	4
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Developed the user interface (UI) for the trading courses list view page.</li> <li>Optimize user experience by creating a user-friendly interface that is easy to use and compatible across multiple devices.</li> <li>Integrate API from backend to display blog/news list, blog/news details, and search function, administrator dashboard</li> <li>Build login and user account management functions.</li> <li>Bug Fixing</li> <li>The project was successfully implemented and is operating in the product environment.</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Reactjs, Nextjs, SCSS - MySQL

## **Portfolio**

(2022 - Current)

Customer	Person project
Description	Introducing personal experiences and experiences, projects and technologies used
Team size	1
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Design and implement the user interface (UI) for the application.</li> <li>Use Reactjs, Nextjs to create components and manage state.</li> <li>Deploy to vercel</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Nextjs, Reactjs, Tailwind CSS

## SucKhoeHot

(Mar 2022 - Current)

Customer	Vinvas
Description	Channel of information about health, life tips
Team size	2
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Optimize user interface on different devices (responsive design).</li> <li>Integrate unique plugins and features like search bar, checkout</li> <li>Create about pages, and contact pages</li> <li>Ensure source code complies with SEO standards and optimizes page loading speed.</li> <li>Development</li> <li>Bug Fixing</li> <li>Deploy to Linux</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Wordpress

## - MySQL

## DauGialbid

(Nov 2021 - Current)

Customer	Vano
Description	Service of providing information content on telecommunications network for customers using MobiFone subscribers
Team size	2
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Optimize user interface on different devices (responsive design).</li> <li>Integrate unique plugins and features like search bar, checkout</li> <li>Create about pages, and contact pages</li> <li>Ensure source code complies with SEO standards and optimizes page loading speed.</li> <li>Development</li> <li>Bug Fixing</li> <li>Deploy to Linux</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Laravel - MySQL

## Vano

(Apr 2022 - Current)

Customer	Vano
Description	Develop a website to introduce Vano.
Team size	1
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Optimize user interface on different devices (responsive design).</li> <li>Integrate unique plugins and features like search bar, checkout</li> <li>Create about pages, and contact pages</li> <li>Ensure source code complies with SEO standards and optimizes page loading speed.</li> <li>Development</li> <li>Bug Fixing</li> <li>Deploy to Linux</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- Wordpress - MySQL